https://www.metalchange.com/policy.html

METALchange.com
is a world wide information trading site and
was established to promote trade in the Precious Metals Industry.
|
Add Listing ]
Privacy Policy
PRIVACY POLICY / TERMS & CONDITIONS : (Updated on March 16, 2009)
This is the Privacy Policy governing your use of the METALchange.com. By using this Site, you consent to our Privacy Policy set out below. All terms not defined in this document have the meanings ascribed to them in the Terms of Use Agreement between you and METALchange.com which by use of this Site you agree to accept.
The Information We Collect
Registration Information: At the time you register to become a User of the Site, you will be asked to complete a registration form which requires you provide information such as your name, address, phone/fax number, email address and other personal information as well as information about your company.
If you submit any information to METALchange.com it may be published on the Site through the publishing tools, including but not limited to Company name, address, phone/fax number, Profile, then you are deemed to have given consent to the publication of such information.
In addition, we gather aggregate statistical information about our Site and Users, such as IP addresses, browser software, operating system, pages viewed, number of sessions, unique visitors and so forth.
We may share certain aggregate information based on analysis of Collected Information with our partners, customers, advertisers or potential Users.
We may use your email address, mailing address, phone number or fax number to contact you regarding notices, surveys, product alerts, new service or product offerings and communications relevant to your use of our Site. We may generate reports and analysis based on the Registration Information for internal analysis, monitoring and marketing decisions.
All of your information may be publicly available on the Site and therefore accessible by any internet user. Any information that you disclose to METALchange.com
becomes public information and you relinquish any proprietary rights (including but not limited to the rights of confidentiality and copyrights) in such information.
Payment Information: METALchange.com will share your Payment Information with banks relevant to the transaction in order to enable transactions to be completed. Any credit card information that you provide through the Site is directly submitted to a payment server of the credit card processing bank. While METALchange.com has in place up-to-date technology and internal procedures to guard your Payment Information against intruders, there is no guarantee that such technology or procedure can eliminate all of the risks of theft, loss or mis-use. METALchange.com shall not be liable to you or any other person for any damages that might result from unauthorized use, publication, disclosure or any other mis-use of Payment Information, including credit card information.
Disclosure of Information :
We reserve the right to disclose your Collected Information to relevant authorities where we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be infringing or threatening to infringe, or who may otherwise be causing injury to or interference with, the title, rights, interests or property of METALchange.com, our Users, customers, partners, other web site users or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities.
We also reserve the right to disclose collected information in response to a subpoena or other judicial order or when we reasonably believe that such disclosure is required by law, regulation or administrative order of any court, governmental or regulatory authority.
Cookies :
We use "cookies" to store specific information about you and track your visits to our Site. It is not uncommon for websites to use cookies to enhance identification of their users. A "cookie" is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can be sent to your computer's hard drive only if you access our Site using the computer. If you do not de-activate or erase the cookie, each time you use the same computer to access our Site, our web servers will be notified of your visit to our Site and in turn we may have knowledge of your visit and the pattern of your usage. Generally, we use cookies to identify you and enable us to access your information so you do not have to re-enter it.
We also use third party advertisements on METALchange.com to support our site.
Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies, DART cookies, and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.
These companies may use the information collected (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. (ie. showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).
If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.
You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.
However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.
This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.
Security Measures
We employ commercially reasonable security methods to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure correct use of information.
As a Registered User, your information can be viewed and edited through your Account which is protected by Password. We recommend that you do not divulge your Password to anyone. Our personnel will never ask you for your Password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited e-mail. If you share a computer with others, you should not choose to save your log-in information (e.g., User ID and Password) on the computer. Remember to sign out of your Account and close your browser window when you have finished your session.
No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secured. As a result, while we try to protect your information, no web site or company, including ourselves, can absolutely ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.
Changes to Privacy Policy
Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be communicated through our posting an amended and restated Privacy Policy on our Site. Our posting the amended and restated Privacy Policy will make such new Privacy Policy immediately effective. You agree that all Collected Information (whether or not collected prior to or after the new policy became effective) will be governed by the newest Privacy Policy then in effect. If you do not agree to the new changes in our Privacy Policy, you should contact METALchange.com in writing and specifically request that METALchange.com remove all of your collected information in METALchange.com possession.
This Privacy Policy was last amended on March 16, 2009.
Your Feedback
METALchange.com welcomes your continuous input regarding our Privacy Policy or our services provided to you. You may send us your comments and responses.
***The Internet's Precious Metals Marketplace***
Email FeedBack |
Privacy Policy |
Metals Update
Scrap Catalytic Converters |
Equipment Finder Service
Metal Industry Equipment
File No:
21079
Friday, 11-Dec-2020 02:15:17 EST
